

# **ARPA NIHAN**

House 251, Lane no 2, East Dolairpar, Dhaka 1236

Phone: 01924489215, 01537023186

Gmail: nihanarpa64@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/arpa-nihan-4080771a0/ Portfolio Website: https://arpa12.github.io/Arpa-Nihan/

Github Link: https://github.com/arpa12

# **PROFESSIONAL PROFILE**

A Concentrated Computer Science and Engineering B.Sc. graduate from Daffodil International University. The long-term goal is to become a reputable IT professional at the technology companies. Worked on Lightship as an English Teacher with 2 years of experiences and also worked on 100 Million Mindset Organization as a Co-Founder and also specialized in Graphic Design with 3 years of experiences and Web Design and WordPress Development with 2 years of experiences. Worked with Foreign clients and as well as Local clients.

## **EDUCATION**

December, 2018 - December, 2022

B. Sc in Computer Science & Engineering, Daffodil International University.

Project: Funding Management System

CGPA: 3.28/4.00

April, 2016 - July, 2018 (HSC) Science, Dhaka City College

GPA: 3.92/5.00

# **LANGUAGES**

- Bangla (Native Proficiency)
- English (Full Professional Proficiency)

## TRAINING PROGRAMS

- Wordpress Development organized by Azharul Rafy sir from YouTube
- Frontend Development (HTML,CSS,Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript,TypeScript, React & Redux, Next JS) from YouTube
- Graphic Design from Coders Trust, Bangladesh

#### **SKILLS**

- Programming Languages
  HTML&CSS, Tailwind CSS Bootstrap, JavaScript, TypeScript,
  React & Redux, Next JS
- Web Desing (basics)
- WordPress Development create a website by WordPress using the theme,plugin with Elementor
- Office Suite Microsoft Office

- Integrated Development Environment Visual Studio Code, Bracket
- Content Creation Adobe Creative Cloud (Photoshop, Illustrator), Filmora
- Leadership Teamwork, Public Speaking, Strategic Planning, Critical thinking,

#### RECENT PROJECTS

# Funding Management System

This is basically web-based fund collection project I created with my team for the final year. Here we created a platform where user can sign up on this platform and submit all valid documents, after checking the validity admin will approve it and then user can create post for raising funds for needed people and can share this post through social media and then funds will be start coming to the finacial needs.

# Saifullah Integrated Resources

This is a website which is based on company profile. I have created this website by WordPress using theme, plugin with Elemntor. This project is provided by a local client.

Website link: https://saifullahintegratedresources.com/

#### Collective Tutorial

This is a website which is based on USA Coaching Center. I have created this website by WordPress using theme, plugin with Elemntor. This project is provided by a local client.

Website link: https://collectivetutorial.com/

## • Telephone Lists.biz

I have created this website with raw coding using HTML,CSS and Bootstrap. This project is provided by a local client. Website link: https://arpa12.github.io/SharpCodelT\_TelephoneLists/index.html

#### Check Weather

I have created this website with raw coding using HTML,CSS and JavaScript . This project is provided by a local client. Website link: https://arpa12.github.io/Check-Weather/

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

March 2023 - October 2023

# Software Developer-fresher, Cloud Production LTD

Working on Website as a Software Developer-fresher. In Frontend Development I am using HTML,CSS,JS,React AND Next js. I have completed my Internship.

January 2021 - Septembar 2023

#### Website Developer, Local

Working on Website as a Frontend Developer and Wordpress Developer. In Frontend Development I am using HTML,CSS and Bootstrap, tailwind, JavaScript, Typescript, React JS and Next Js and in WordPress I am using theme ,plugin with Elemntor.

June 2020 - March 2023

# Graphic Designer, Fiverr

I am a Graphic Designer at Fiverr marketplace and completed orders which is given by International Client

December 2018 - November 2020

**Assistant Teacher, Lightship** 

# **References:**

Md. Zabirul Islam

Lecturer

Daffodil International University zabirul.cse@diu.edu.bd Cell: +8801521307471

**Israt Jahan** 

Lecturer

Daffodil International University isratjahan.cse@diu.edu.bd Cell: +8801794362263